[
  {
    "id": "293",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What type of storage gateway is used for archiving of flat files only?",
      "answers": [
        "File Gateway",
        "Volume Gateway Stored Volumes",
        "Volume Gateway Cached Volumes",
        "Gateway Virtual Tape Library (VTL)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["File Gateway"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "294",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What type of storage gateway stores the entire dataset on site and is asychronously backed up to S3?",
      "answers": [
        "File Gateway",
        "Volume Gateway Stored Volumes",
        "Volume Gateway Cached Volumes",
        "Gateway Virtual Tape Library (VTL)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Volume Gateway Stored Volumes"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "295",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What type of storage gateway stores the entire dataset on S3 and the most frequently accessed data is cached on site?",
      "answers": [
        "File Gateway",
        "Volume Gateway Stored Volumes",
        "Volume Gateway Cached Volumes",
        "Gateway Virtual Tape Library (VTL)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Volume Gateway Cached Volumes"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "296",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What type of storage gateway is used for back up and uses popular back up applications like NetBackup, Backup Exec, Veem, etc?",
      "answers": [
        "File Gateway",
        "Volume Gateway Stored Volumes",
        "Volume Gateway Cached Volumes",
        "Gateway Virtual Tape Library (VTL)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Gateway Virtual Tape Library (VTL)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "297",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which type of storage gateway is used for block-based storage, like for storing OSs or databases?",
      "answers": [
        "File Gateway",
        "Volume Gateway"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Volume Gateway"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "298",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which type of storage gateway is used for object-based storage, like for storing flat files?",
      "answers": [
        "File Gateway",
        "Volume Gateway"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["File Gateway"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "299",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which type of storage gateway lets you use S3 as your primary storage while retaining frequently accessed data locally?",
      "answers": [
        "File Gateway",
        "Volume Gateway Stored Volumes",
        "Volume Gateway Cached Volumes",
        "Gateway Virtual Tape Library (VTL)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Volume Gateway Cached Volumes"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "300",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which type of storage gateway offers a durable, cost-effective solution to archive your data in the AWS cloud, leveraging your existing tape backup application?",
      "answers": [
        "File Gateway",
        "Volume Gateway Stored Volumes",
        "Volume Gateway Cached Volumes",
        "Gateway Virtual Tape Library (VTL)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Gateway Virtual Tape Library (VTL)"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "301",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which type of storage gateway lets you store your primary data locally, while asynchronously backing up that data to AWS?",
      "answers": [
        "File Gateway",
        "Volume Gateway Stored Volumes",
        "Volume Gateway Cached Volumes",
        "Gateway Virtual Tape Library (VTL)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Volume Gateway Stored Volumes"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "302",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which type of storage gateway presents your applications with disk volumes using the iSCSI block protocol?",
      "answers": [
        "File Gateway",
        "Volume Gateway"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Volume Gateway"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "303",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 3",
      "question": "Storage Gateway can connect to AWS via which of these?",
      "answers": [
        "Direct Connect",
        "the internet",
        "via your VPC",
        "Snowball"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Direct Connect", "the internet", "via your VPC"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "304",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which type of Storage Gateway stores your files as objects in your S3 buckets, which are accessed through a Networked File System (NFS) mount point?",
      "answers": [
        "File Gateway",
        "Volume Gateway Stored Volumes",
        "Volume Gateway Cached Volumes",
        "Gateway Virtual Tape Library (VTL)"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["File Gateway"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "305",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "S3",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Storage Gateway appliance is available for download as a virtual machine image that you install in your datacenter on a hypervisor?",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["true"]
    }
  }
]
